{
  "subject": "mathematics",
  "grade": "second_grade",
  "question_count": 150,
  "questions": [
    {
      "id": "mathematics_2_8902",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "second_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 3,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 11 + 8?",
      "answer": "19",
      "variables": {
        "a": 11,
        "b": 8,
        "result": 19
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_2_2971",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "second_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 1,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 16 - 15?",
      "answer": "1",
      "variables": {
        "a": 16,
        "b": 15,
        "result": 1
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_2_7278",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "second_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 1,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 12 - 3?",
      "answer": "9",
      "variables": {
        "a": 12,
        "b": 3,
        "result": 9
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_2_9544",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "second_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 2,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 17 + 10?",
      "answer": "27",
      "variables": {
        "a": 17,
        "b": 10,
        "result": 27
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_2_2188",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "second_grade",
      "topic": "division",
      "difficulty": 4,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 121 ÷ 11?",
      "answer": "11",
      "variables": {
        "a": 121,
        "b": 11,
        "result": 11
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_2_4511",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "second_grade",
      "topic": "multiplication",
      "difficulty": 2,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 6 × 11?",
      "answer": "66",
      "variables": {
        "a": 6,
        "b": 11,
        "result": 66
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_2_3970",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "second_grade",
      "topic": "division",
      "difficulty": 4,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 60 ÷ 5?",
      "answer": "12",
      "variables": {
        "a": 60,
        "b": 5,
        "result": 12
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_2_9991",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "second_grade",
      "topic": "multiplication",
      "difficulty": 2,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 9 × 8?",
      "answer": "72",
      "variables": {
        "a": 9,
        "b": 8,
        "result": 72
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_2_5743",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "second_grade",
      "topic": "multiplication",
      "difficulty": 4,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 11 × 10?",
      "answer": "110",
      "variables": {
        "a": 11,
        "b": 10,
        "result": 110
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_2_9247",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "second_grade",
      "topic": "division",
      "difficulty": 4,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 48 ÷ 4?",
      "answer": "12",
      "variables": {
        "a": 48,
        "b": 4,
        "result": 12
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_2_6641",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "second_grade",
      "topic": "multiplication",
      "difficulty": 3,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 10 × 1?",
      "answer": "10",
      "variables": {
        "a": 10,
        "b": 1,
        "result": 10
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_2_7441",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "second_grade",
      "topic": "division",
      "difficulty": 4,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 99 ÷ 9?",
      "answer": "11",
      "variables": {
        "a": 99,
        "b": 9,
        "result": 11
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_2_2851",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "second_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 3,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 3 - 2?",
      "answer": "1",
      "variables": {
        "a": 3,
        "b": 2,
        "result": 1
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_2_7478",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "second_grade",
      "topic": "division",
      "difficulty": 4,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 63 ÷ 9?",
      "answer": "7",
      "variables": {
        "a": 63,
        "b": 9,
        "result": 7
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_2_8128",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "second_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 3,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 13 - 11?",
      "answer": "2",
      "variables": {
        "a": 13,
        "b": 11,
        "result": 2
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_2_7412",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "second_grade",
      "topic": "division",
      "difficulty": 4,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 120 ÷ 10?",
      "answer": "12",
      "variables": {
        "a": 120,
        "b": 10,
        "result": 12
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_2_3748",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "second_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 1,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 12 + 16?",
      "answer": "28",
      "variables": {
        "a": 12,
        "b": 16,
        "result": 28
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_2_3956",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "second_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 2,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 20 - 17?",
      "answer": "3",
      "variables": {
        "a": 20,
        "b": 17,
        "result": 3
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_2_8342",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "second_grade",
      "topic": "division",
      "difficulty": 3,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 36 ÷ 4?",
      "answer": "9",
      "variables": {
        "a": 36,
        "b": 4,
        "result": 9
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_2_7157",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "second_grade",
      "topic": "division",
      "difficulty": 2,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 63 ÷ 7?",
      "answer": "9",
      "variables": {
        "a": 63,
        "b": 7,
        "result": 9
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_2_2418",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "second_grade",
      "topic": "division",
      "difficulty": 4,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 6 ÷ 3?",
      "answer": "2",
      "variables": {
        "a": 6,
        "b": 3,
        "result": 2
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_2_2020",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "second_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 2,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 20 + 10?",
      "answer": "30",
      "variables": {
        "a": 20,
        "b": 10,
        "result": 30
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_2_2603",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "second_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 1,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 1 + 18?",
      "answer": "19",
      "variables": {
        "a": 1,
        "b": 18,
        "result": 19
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_2_4670",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "second_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 2,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 2 - 1?",
      "answer": "1",
      "variables": {
        "a": 2,
        "b": 1,
        "result": 1
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_2_2209",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "second_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 3,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 20 + 11?",
      "answer": "31",
      "variables": {
        "a": 20,
        "b": 11,
        "result": 31
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_2_3056",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "second_grade",
      "topic": "division",
      "difficulty": 3,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 77 ÷ 11?",
      "answer": "7",
      "variables": {
        "a": 77,
        "b": 11,
        "result": 7
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_2_6849",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "second_grade",
      "topic": "division",
      "difficulty": 4,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 96 ÷ 8?",
      "answer": "12",
      "variables": {
        "a": 96,
        "b": 8,
        "result": 12
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_2_6672",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "second_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 3,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 6 + 3?",
      "answer": "9",
      "variables": {
        "a": 6,
        "b": 3,
        "result": 9
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_2_8409",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "second_grade",
      "topic": "multiplication",
      "difficulty": 3,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 8 × 12?",
      "answer": "96",
      "variables": {
        "a": 8,
        "b": 12,
        "result": 96
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_2_8540",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "second_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 1,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 17 + 11?",
      "answer": "28",
      "variables": {
        "a": 17,
        "b": 11,
        "result": 28
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_2_4171",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "second_grade",
      "topic": "division",
      "difficulty": 2,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 25 ÷ 5?",
      "answer": "5",
      "variables": {
        "a": 25,
        "b": 5,
        "result": 5
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_2_3949",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "second_grade",
      "topic": "division",
      "difficulty": 4,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 15 ÷ 3?",
      "answer": "5",
      "variables": {
        "a": 15,
        "b": 3,
        "result": 5
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_2_2229",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "second_grade",
      "topic": "multiplication",
      "difficulty": 3,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 11 × 9?",
      "answer": "99",
      "variables": {
        "a": 11,
        "b": 9,
        "result": 99
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_2_4814",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "second_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 2,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 14 + 18?",
      "answer": "32",
      "variables": {
        "a": 14,
        "b": 18,
        "result": 32
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_2_9790",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "second_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 3,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 7 + 20?",
      "answer": "27",
      "variables": {
        "a": 7,
        "b": 20,
        "result": 27
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_2_7904",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "second_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 3,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 17 + 5?",
      "answer": "22",
      "variables": {
        "a": 17,
        "b": 5,
        "result": 22
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_2_5774",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "second_grade",
      "topic": "multiplication",
      "difficulty": 2,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 12 × 1?",
      "answer": "12",
      "variables": {
        "a": 12,
        "b": 1,
        "result": 12
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_2_4970",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "second_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 2,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 11 + 4?",
      "answer": "15",
      "variables": {
        "a": 11,
        "b": 4,
        "result": 15
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_2_6231",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "second_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 2,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 9 + 2?",
      "answer": "11",
      "variables": {
        "a": 9,
        "b": 2,
        "result": 11
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_2_7223",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "second_grade",
      "topic": "multiplication",
      "difficulty": 3,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 1 × 12?",
      "answer": "12",
      "variables": {
        "a": 1,
        "b": 12,
        "result": 12
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_2_4074",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "second_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 1,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 9 + 19?",
      "answer": "28",
      "variables": {
        "a": 9,
        "b": 19,
        "result": 28
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_2_4440",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "second_grade",
      "topic": "multiplication",
      "difficulty": 3,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 2 × 7?",
      "answer": "14",
      "variables": {
        "a": 2,
        "b": 7,
        "result": 14
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_2_4182",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "second_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 3,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 15 + 7?",
      "answer": "22",
      "variables": {
        "a": 15,
        "b": 7,
        "result": 22
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_2_2134",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "second_grade",
      "topic": "division",
      "difficulty": 3,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 88 ÷ 11?",
      "answer": "8",
      "variables": {
        "a": 88,
        "b": 11,
        "result": 8
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_2_6776",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "second_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 3,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 18 - 2?",
      "answer": "16",
      "variables": {
        "a": 18,
        "b": 2,
        "result": 16
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_2_1950",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "second_grade",
      "topic": "division",
      "difficulty": 4,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 18 ÷ 9?",
      "answer": "2",
      "variables": {
        "a": 18,
        "b": 9,
        "result": 2
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_2_6126",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "second_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 1,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 12 + 8?",
      "answer": "20",
      "variables": {
        "a": 12,
        "b": 8,
        "result": 20
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_2_9119",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "second_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 1,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 15 - 12?",
      "answer": "3",
      "variables": {
        "a": 15,
        "b": 12,
        "result": 3
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_2_9026",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "second_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 2,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 16 + 17?",
      "answer": "33",
      "variables": {
        "a": 16,
        "b": 17,
        "result": 33
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_2_2366",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "second_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 1,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 14 + 8?",
      "answer": "22",
      "variables": {
        "a": 14,
        "b": 8,
        "result": 22
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_2_6313",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "second_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 2,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 5 + 4?",
      "answer": "9",
      "variables": {
        "a": 5,
        "b": 4,
        "result": 9
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_2_7410",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "second_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 3,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 7 + 20?",
      "answer": "27",
      "variables": {
        "a": 7,
        "b": 20,
        "result": 27
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_2_2387",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "second_grade",
      "topic": "multiplication",
      "difficulty": 2,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 6 × 9?",
      "answer": "54",
      "variables": {
        "a": 6,
        "b": 9,
        "result": 54
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_2_4385",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "second_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 1,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 7 + 1?",
      "answer": "8",
      "variables": {
        "a": 7,
        "b": 1,
        "result": 8
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_2_7185",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "second_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 2,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 17 - 10?",
      "answer": "7",
      "variables": {
        "a": 17,
        "b": 10,
        "result": 7
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_2_2202",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "second_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 2,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 16 - 6?",
      "answer": "10",
      "variables": {
        "a": 16,
        "b": 6,
        "result": 10
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_2_1572",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "second_grade",
      "topic": "division",
      "difficulty": 3,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 22 ÷ 2?",
      "answer": "11",
      "variables": {
        "a": 22,
        "b": 2,
        "result": 11
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_2_4709",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "second_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 2,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 16 + 11?",
      "answer": "27",
      "variables": {
        "a": 16,
        "b": 11,
        "result": 27
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_2_1783",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "second_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 1,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 14 + 20?",
      "answer": "34",
      "variables": {
        "a": 14,
        "b": 20,
        "result": 34
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_2_1694",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "second_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 2,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 20 - 16?",
      "answer": "4",
      "variables": {
        "a": 20,
        "b": 16,
        "result": 4
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_2_2131",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "second_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 2,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 16 + 9?",
      "answer": "25",
      "variables": {
        "a": 16,
        "b": 9,
        "result": 25
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_2_5552",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "second_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 1,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 8 - 6?",
      "answer": "2",
      "variables": {
        "a": 8,
        "b": 6,
        "result": 2
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_2_1920",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "second_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 1,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 3 + 20?",
      "answer": "23",
      "variables": {
        "a": 3,
        "b": 20,
        "result": 23
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_2_7523",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "second_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 2,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 15 - 15?",
      "answer": "0",
      "variables": {
        "a": 15,
        "b": 15,
        "result": 0
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_2_4140",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "second_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 1,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 19 - 7?",
      "answer": "12",
      "variables": {
        "a": 19,
        "b": 7,
        "result": 12
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_2_3190",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "second_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 1,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 4 + 12?",
      "answer": "16",
      "variables": {
        "a": 4,
        "b": 12,
        "result": 16
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_2_6459",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "second_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 3,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 16 + 10?",
      "answer": "26",
      "variables": {
        "a": 16,
        "b": 10,
        "result": 26
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_2_3707",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "second_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 3,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 8 + 9?",
      "answer": "17",
      "variables": {
        "a": 8,
        "b": 9,
        "result": 17
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_2_3159",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "second_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 1,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 18 - 4?",
      "answer": "14",
      "variables": {
        "a": 18,
        "b": 4,
        "result": 14
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_2_1049",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "second_grade",
      "topic": "multiplication",
      "difficulty": 2,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 7 × 10?",
      "answer": "70",
      "variables": {
        "a": 7,
        "b": 10,
        "result": 70
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_2_5334",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "second_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 2,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 12 - 3?",
      "answer": "9",
      "variables": {
        "a": 12,
        "b": 3,
        "result": 9
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_2_5316",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "second_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 3,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 11 - 4?",
      "answer": "7",
      "variables": {
        "a": 11,
        "b": 4,
        "result": 7
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_2_8793",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "second_grade",
      "topic": "division",
      "difficulty": 2,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 81 ÷ 9?",
      "answer": "9",
      "variables": {
        "a": 81,
        "b": 9,
        "result": 9
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_2_1465",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "second_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 2,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 16 - 14?",
      "answer": "2",
      "variables": {
        "a": 16,
        "b": 14,
        "result": 2
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_2_7339",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "second_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 3,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 15 - 6?",
      "answer": "9",
      "variables": {
        "a": 15,
        "b": 6,
        "result": 9
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_2_7027",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "second_grade",
      "topic": "multiplication",
      "difficulty": 3,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 5 × 10?",
      "answer": "50",
      "variables": {
        "a": 5,
        "b": 10,
        "result": 50
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_2_5392",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "second_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 1,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 18 + 6?",
      "answer": "24",
      "variables": {
        "a": 18,
        "b": 6,
        "result": 24
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_2_3167",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "second_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 2,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 10 + 5?",
      "answer": "15",
      "variables": {
        "a": 10,
        "b": 5,
        "result": 15
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_2_1535",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "second_grade",
      "topic": "division",
      "difficulty": 2,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 42 ÷ 7?",
      "answer": "6",
      "variables": {
        "a": 42,
        "b": 7,
        "result": 6
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_2_9598",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "second_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 2,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 20 - 2?",
      "answer": "18",
      "variables": {
        "a": 20,
        "b": 2,
        "result": 18
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_2_3192",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "second_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 1,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 18 - 3?",
      "answer": "15",
      "variables": {
        "a": 18,
        "b": 3,
        "result": 15
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_2_8512",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "second_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 3,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 12 + 10?",
      "answer": "22",
      "variables": {
        "a": 12,
        "b": 10,
        "result": 22
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_2_6885",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "second_grade",
      "topic": "division",
      "difficulty": 2,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 42 ÷ 6?",
      "answer": "7",
      "variables": {
        "a": 42,
        "b": 6,
        "result": 7
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_2_9907",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "second_grade",
      "topic": "division",
      "difficulty": 2,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 27 ÷ 3?",
      "answer": "9",
      "variables": {
        "a": 27,
        "b": 3,
        "result": 9
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_2_4954",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "second_grade",
      "topic": "division",
      "difficulty": 3,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 9 ÷ 1?",
      "answer": "9",
      "variables": {
        "a": 9,
        "b": 1,
        "result": 9
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_2_8986",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "second_grade",
      "topic": "division",
      "difficulty": 3,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 72 ÷ 9?",
      "answer": "8",
      "variables": {
        "a": 72,
        "b": 9,
        "result": 8
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_2_9566",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "second_grade",
      "topic": "division",
      "difficulty": 2,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 12 ÷ 3?",
      "answer": "4",
      "variables": {
        "a": 12,
        "b": 3,
        "result": 4
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_2_9366",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "second_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 3,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 11 - 7?",
      "answer": "4",
      "variables": {
        "a": 11,
        "b": 7,
        "result": 4
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_2_9467",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "second_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 2,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 14 + 11?",
      "answer": "25",
      "variables": {
        "a": 14,
        "b": 11,
        "result": 25
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_2_1477",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "second_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 3,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 14 - 4?",
      "answer": "10",
      "variables": {
        "a": 14,
        "b": 4,
        "result": 10
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_2_2401",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "second_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 1,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 11 - 7?",
      "answer": "4",
      "variables": {
        "a": 11,
        "b": 7,
        "result": 4
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_2_1880",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "second_grade",
      "topic": "division",
      "difficulty": 4,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 33 ÷ 3?",
      "answer": "11",
      "variables": {
        "a": 33,
        "b": 3,
        "result": 11
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_2_3667",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "second_grade",
      "topic": "division",
      "difficulty": 3,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 24 ÷ 4?",
      "answer": "6",
      "variables": {
        "a": 24,
        "b": 4,
        "result": 6
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_2_4143",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "second_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 2,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 5 + 13?",
      "answer": "18",
      "variables": {
        "a": 5,
        "b": 13,
        "result": 18
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_2_8870",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "second_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 1,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 18 + 10?",
      "answer": "28",
      "variables": {
        "a": 18,
        "b": 10,
        "result": 28
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_2_4697",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "second_grade",
      "topic": "division",
      "difficulty": 4,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 96 ÷ 8?",
      "answer": "12",
      "variables": {
        "a": 96,
        "b": 8,
        "result": 12
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_2_6309",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "second_grade",
      "topic": "multiplication",
      "difficulty": 3,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 2 × 10?",
      "answer": "20",
      "variables": {
        "a": 2,
        "b": 10,
        "result": 20
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_2_1094",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "second_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 3,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 8 + 16?",
      "answer": "24",
      "variables": {
        "a": 8,
        "b": 16,
        "result": 24
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_2_2465",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "second_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 3,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 9 - 4?",
      "answer": "5",
      "variables": {
        "a": 9,
        "b": 4,
        "result": 5
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_2_7359",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "second_grade",
      "topic": "multiplication",
      "difficulty": 3,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 5 × 10?",
      "answer": "50",
      "variables": {
        "a": 5,
        "b": 10,
        "result": 50
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_2_2011",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "second_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 3,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 12 + 15?",
      "answer": "27",
      "variables": {
        "a": 12,
        "b": 15,
        "result": 27
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_2_2058",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "second_grade",
      "topic": "multiplication",
      "difficulty": 2,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 1 × 5?",
      "answer": "5",
      "variables": {
        "a": 1,
        "b": 5,
        "result": 5
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_2_5956",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "second_grade",
      "topic": "division",
      "difficulty": 2,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 88 ÷ 11?",
      "answer": "8",
      "variables": {
        "a": 88,
        "b": 11,
        "result": 8
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_2_3164",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "second_grade",
      "topic": "multiplication",
      "difficulty": 4,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 12 × 6?",
      "answer": "72",
      "variables": {
        "a": 12,
        "b": 6,
        "result": 72
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_2_9203",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "second_grade",
      "topic": "division",
      "difficulty": 2,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 4 ÷ 4?",
      "answer": "1",
      "variables": {
        "a": 4,
        "b": 4,
        "result": 1
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_2_9318",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "second_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 2,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 6 + 12?",
      "answer": "18",
      "variables": {
        "a": 6,
        "b": 12,
        "result": 18
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_2_6536",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "second_grade",
      "topic": "multiplication",
      "difficulty": 4,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 10 × 10?",
      "answer": "100",
      "variables": {
        "a": 10,
        "b": 10,
        "result": 100
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_2_4111",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "second_grade",
      "topic": "division",
      "difficulty": 4,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 120 ÷ 12?",
      "answer": "10",
      "variables": {
        "a": 120,
        "b": 12,
        "result": 10
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_2_3147",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "second_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 3,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 8 - 6?",
      "answer": "2",
      "variables": {
        "a": 8,
        "b": 6,
        "result": 2
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_2_6244",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "second_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 1,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 17 - 16?",
      "answer": "1",
      "variables": {
        "a": 17,
        "b": 16,
        "result": 1
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_2_5036",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "second_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 3,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 18 - 4?",
      "answer": "14",
      "variables": {
        "a": 18,
        "b": 4,
        "result": 14
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_2_9580",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "second_grade",
      "topic": "multiplication",
      "difficulty": 2,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 7 × 4?",
      "answer": "28",
      "variables": {
        "a": 7,
        "b": 4,
        "result": 28
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_2_7503",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "second_grade",
      "topic": "multiplication",
      "difficulty": 4,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 9 × 2?",
      "answer": "18",
      "variables": {
        "a": 9,
        "b": 2,
        "result": 18
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_2_6152",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "second_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 2,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 9 - 2?",
      "answer": "7",
      "variables": {
        "a": 9,
        "b": 2,
        "result": 7
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_2_4962",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "second_grade",
      "topic": "multiplication",
      "difficulty": 3,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 6 × 2?",
      "answer": "12",
      "variables": {
        "a": 6,
        "b": 2,
        "result": 12
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_2_9204",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "second_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 3,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 3 + 6?",
      "answer": "9",
      "variables": {
        "a": 3,
        "b": 6,
        "result": 9
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_2_4005",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "second_grade",
      "topic": "multiplication",
      "difficulty": 2,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 11 × 6?",
      "answer": "66",
      "variables": {
        "a": 11,
        "b": 6,
        "result": 66
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_2_1338",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "second_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 2,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 20 - 4?",
      "answer": "16",
      "variables": {
        "a": 20,
        "b": 4,
        "result": 16
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_2_6488",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "second_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 2,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 1 - 1?",
      "answer": "0",
      "variables": {
        "a": 1,
        "b": 1,
        "result": 0
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_2_9945",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "second_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 3,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 12 + 8?",
      "answer": "20",
      "variables": {
        "a": 12,
        "b": 8,
        "result": 20
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_2_7844",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "second_grade",
      "topic": "multiplication",
      "difficulty": 3,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 8 × 3?",
      "answer": "24",
      "variables": {
        "a": 8,
        "b": 3,
        "result": 24
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_2_4045",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "second_grade",
      "topic": "division",
      "difficulty": 2,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 120 ÷ 10?",
      "answer": "12",
      "variables": {
        "a": 120,
        "b": 10,
        "result": 12
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_2_5804",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "second_grade",
      "topic": "division",
      "difficulty": 2,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 44 ÷ 11?",
      "answer": "4",
      "variables": {
        "a": 44,
        "b": 11,
        "result": 4
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_2_7395",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "second_grade",
      "topic": "division",
      "difficulty": 4,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 36 ÷ 12?",
      "answer": "3",
      "variables": {
        "a": 36,
        "b": 12,
        "result": 3
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_2_8162",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "second_grade",
      "topic": "multiplication",
      "difficulty": 2,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 3 × 12?",
      "answer": "36",
      "variables": {
        "a": 3,
        "b": 12,
        "result": 36
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_2_3317",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "second_grade",
      "topic": "division",
      "difficulty": 3,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 6 ÷ 1?",
      "answer": "6",
      "variables": {
        "a": 6,
        "b": 1,
        "result": 6
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_2_1648",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "second_grade",
      "topic": "division",
      "difficulty": 3,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 30 ÷ 5?",
      "answer": "6",
      "variables": {
        "a": 30,
        "b": 5,
        "result": 6
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_2_8036",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "second_grade",
      "topic": "multiplication",
      "difficulty": 2,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 2 × 2?",
      "answer": "4",
      "variables": {
        "a": 2,
        "b": 2,
        "result": 4
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_2_3766",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "second_grade",
      "topic": "multiplication",
      "difficulty": 4,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 7 × 8?",
      "answer": "56",
      "variables": {
        "a": 7,
        "b": 8,
        "result": 56
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_2_4920",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "second_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 3,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 10 + 15?",
      "answer": "25",
      "variables": {
        "a": 10,
        "b": 15,
        "result": 25
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_2_5129",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "second_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 1,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 14 - 4?",
      "answer": "10",
      "variables": {
        "a": 14,
        "b": 4,
        "result": 10
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_2_9539",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "second_grade",
      "topic": "division",
      "difficulty": 4,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 18 ÷ 9?",
      "answer": "2",
      "variables": {
        "a": 18,
        "b": 9,
        "result": 2
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_2_2954",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "second_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 1,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 14 - 1?",
      "answer": "13",
      "variables": {
        "a": 14,
        "b": 1,
        "result": 13
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_2_9976",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "second_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 2,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 7 + 12?",
      "answer": "19",
      "variables": {
        "a": 7,
        "b": 12,
        "result": 19
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_2_8033",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "second_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 3,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 14 - 13?",
      "answer": "1",
      "variables": {
        "a": 14,
        "b": 13,
        "result": 1
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_2_4864",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "second_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 1,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 8 - 5?",
      "answer": "3",
      "variables": {
        "a": 8,
        "b": 5,
        "result": 3
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_2_8133",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "second_grade",
      "topic": "multiplication",
      "difficulty": 4,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 3 × 6?",
      "answer": "18",
      "variables": {
        "a": 3,
        "b": 6,
        "result": 18
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_2_1949",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "second_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 3,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 18 - 9?",
      "answer": "9",
      "variables": {
        "a": 18,
        "b": 9,
        "result": 9
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_2_1391",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "second_grade",
      "topic": "multiplication",
      "difficulty": 2,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 2 × 1?",
      "answer": "2",
      "variables": {
        "a": 2,
        "b": 1,
        "result": 2
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_2_7484",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "second_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 1,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 14 + 18?",
      "answer": "32",
      "variables": {
        "a": 14,
        "b": 18,
        "result": 32
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_2_7035",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "second_grade",
      "topic": "multiplication",
      "difficulty": 4,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 12 × 4?",
      "answer": "48",
      "variables": {
        "a": 12,
        "b": 4,
        "result": 48
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_2_2345",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "second_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 2,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 14 - 5?",
      "answer": "9",
      "variables": {
        "a": 14,
        "b": 5,
        "result": 9
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_2_2607",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "second_grade",
      "topic": "multiplication",
      "difficulty": 4,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 8 × 9?",
      "answer": "72",
      "variables": {
        "a": 8,
        "b": 9,
        "result": 72
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_2_1889",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "second_grade",
      "topic": "division",
      "difficulty": 2,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 42 ÷ 6?",
      "answer": "7",
      "variables": {
        "a": 42,
        "b": 6,
        "result": 7
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_2_8287",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "second_grade",
      "topic": "division",
      "difficulty": 2,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 3 ÷ 3?",
      "answer": "1",
      "variables": {
        "a": 3,
        "b": 3,
        "result": 1
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_2_8607",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "second_grade",
      "topic": "multiplication",
      "difficulty": 4,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 6 × 3?",
      "answer": "18",
      "variables": {
        "a": 6,
        "b": 3,
        "result": 18
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_2_9909",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "second_grade",
      "topic": "multiplication",
      "difficulty": 3,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 2 × 6?",
      "answer": "12",
      "variables": {
        "a": 2,
        "b": 6,
        "result": 12
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_2_3297",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "second_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 3,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 14 - 11?",
      "answer": "3",
      "variables": {
        "a": 14,
        "b": 11,
        "result": 3
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_2_9280",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "second_grade",
      "topic": "division",
      "difficulty": 3,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 45 ÷ 9?",
      "answer": "5",
      "variables": {
        "a": 45,
        "b": 9,
        "result": 5
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_2_1850",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "second_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 2,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 13 - 6?",
      "answer": "7",
      "variables": {
        "a": 13,
        "b": 6,
        "result": 7
      }
    }
  ]
}